你慢一点，报纸不会在 半夜一点就全部卖光的
Slow down! The paper won't be sold out at 1:00 in the morning.
我好兴奋 第一次有我的剧评
I'm excited! I've never been reviewed before!
你演国王演得太精采了 我真的好欣赏，真的
You were so amazing as the king! I'm really impressed.
不过你知道吗？
But you know what?
我觉得下一次啊 你应该考虑要穿穿内裤
You might wanna wear underwear next time.
因为当你登上王位的时候 观众可以看到你的…
When you sat on the throne,you could see your...
…皇家的东西
... royal subjects.
那个年代没有人穿内裤的
No one wore underwear back then.
我相信评论家会欣赏你的真实性表演的
I' m sure the critics appreciated your authenticity.
顺便说一句，不错的生殖器
Nice genitals, by the way.
谢谢兄弟
Thanks, man.
有了，在这儿
Here it is! Here it is!
唯一比没大脑又孩子气的导演还要烂的是…
"The only thing worse than the mindless adolescent direction...
…乔伊崔比亚尼对国王的超级逊的诠释
...was Joseph Tribbiani's disturbingly unskilled portrayal of the king."
那只是一个人的意见
Okay,look. That is one guy's opinion.
菲比，念你的
All right? Pheebs,read yours.
“唯一比没大脑又孩子气的导演 还要烂的是…”
"The only thing worse than the mindless,adolescent direction"
谁念一念别家报纸可以吗？
Anybody have a different paper?
罗斯，念你的
Ross,read yours.
我不想念
I don't want to.
最有趣的时刻是当国王被砍头不再讲话的时候
"The one enjoyable moment is when the king is beheaded and speaks no more. "
乔伊，他们根本不懂他们在讲什么
Joey,they don't know what they're talking about.
那不一定
Maybe they do.
演了十年还混不出名堂 不是因为我烂是什么
I've done this 10 years and I'm nowhere. There's gotta be a reason.
别这样嘛，你现在是努力阶段
Come on,you're just paying your dues.
不…太难了
No,no,no. It's too hard.
这不值得，我不干了
It's not worth it. I quit.
别这样…
Come on,Joey!
等一下…
Wait,wait one minute. Wait a minute.
包你听了会回心转意的
I believe this will change your mind.
在这出平凡的戏里 乔伊崔比亚尼成功地跃上另一美妙新境界…
"ln a mediocre play,Joseph Tribbiani achieved brilliant levels of
接153页
Continued on page 153.
…超级烂
sucking."
六人行 第2季 第10集 洛斯
The One With Russ
还有什么是你想干的吗
Is there anything else you wanted to be?
我不知道
I don't know.
小时候，我的志愿是当兽医
I used to want to be a vet.
然后我发现我必须要把手 伸到牛的什么的里面
Then I found out you have to put your hands into cows.
你好吗？
Are you okay?
很好，只是水深火热的一天
Just a tough day at work,you know?
剑龙倒了，困住一个小孩
Stegosaurus fell over,trapped a kid.
我认得这件夹克 这是搞笑巴比的夹克
I know this jacket. This is Fun Bobby's jacket!
他在哪里？他在，对不对？
Where is he? He's here,isn't he?
或许 别耍我
-Maybe. -Don't toy with me.
盖勒
Geller!
搞笑巴比
Hey,Fun Bobby!
你有去健身啊？
Hey! You been working out?
才没有呢
Not at all.
我爱这家伙
I love this guy!
好高兴听到 你又跟我妹妹在一起了
I'm psyched to hear you're back with Monica.
我们都是 我错过了什么吗？
-You and me both! -So what'd I miss?
我们只是让乔伊觉得好过一点
We were trying to make Joey feel better.
需要我把你举起来吗？
Need me to pick you up?
不，我没事了，真的
No,I'm all right,man.
不，我要把你举起来
No,I'm picking you up!
不，真的，我不需要…
No,seriously. I don't need you to
好吧，还是有用
It still works!
在我走之前 有谁还要被我给举起来的？
Before I go,does anybody else need to be picked up?
我还是走好了
I'm still gonna go.
待会儿见了，拜拜
See you later,babe.
我们要公开亲热 大家的眼睛请回避一下
Public display of affection coming up. You can avert your eyes.
再见…
See you.
这个搞笑巴比好棒
Fun Bobby is so great.
可不是嘛
Oh,isn't he?
我认为这一回我们会定下来 他让我觉得好棒
I think this time it may work with him. He makes me feel so good.
过去两个月我一直觉得好郁闷 没有工作，没有男友
I've been feeling so lousy lately. No job,no boyfriend.
至少现在我的杯子是半满了
Well,at least my cup is half full.
半满的“爱…”
Half full of love!
他为了庆祝我们的双周庆 周末要带我去他表哥的小木屋
For our two-week anniversary,he's taking me to his cousin's cabin.
“爱…的小屋”
Cabin of love!
我们今晚喝了好多酒
We went through a lot of wine tonight.
真的？我才喝了两杯
I only had two glasses.
我只喝了一杯
I had a glass.
两杯
Two.
我喝了一杯
I had one glass.
我用这可爱的…
I had a mug full in this...
…“我在自然历史博物馆看到骨头了”喝了一杯
... I-got-boned-at-the- Museum-of-Natural-History mug.
这么说的话，顶多两瓶
Okay,so that's what? Two bottles.
可是这里有五个瓶子
And yet somehow we went through five?
那又怎么样，他今晚喝多了
So what? So he drank a lot tonight.
是呀，不过现在我想起来…
Now that I think about it,I don't think...
我记得搞笑巴比酒不离手
...I've ever seen Fun Bobby without a drink.
你们有没有注意过 他故事的开头总是…
And did you notice how he always starts his stories with...
“我喝得烂醉了” 或者是“我们好醉了”
... "Okay,I was so wasted!" or "Oh,we were so bombed!"
或者是“我醒来以后发现 我在康涅狄格州的一辆清道车里面”
"So I wake up and I'm in this dumpster in Connecticut!"
莫妮卡，你们约会时 他有没有喝过酒？
Have you been with him when he wasn't drinking?
只是恰巧而已 我们去的地方都会喝酒的
We just happen to go to a lot of places where you might drink.
我是说去品酒会 怎么可能不来杯酒的
How do you go to a wine-tasting without having a drink?
或者是去俱乐部或是去…
Or to a club,or to the...
…动物园
...zoo.
中央公园
瑞秋，里面有没有脱脂奶？
Rach,does this have nonfat milk?
不知道，你试试看吧
I don't know,taste it.
太迟了，抱歉，你喝过了
Too late,you already had some.
我们把这都弄成爱尔兰咖啡（里面掺有威士忌）怎么样？
What do you say we make these coffees lrish?
蛋糕！
Cake!
对，我们去拿蛋糕
Yeah,we're gonna get some cake.
我发现你最近好像把很多东西 都弄成爱尔兰式的
It seems like you've been making an awful lot of stuff "lrish" lately.
我很想弄成比利时式的 可是饼干很难塞进酒瓶子里
I'd make them Belgian,but the waffles are hard to get into that flask.
好吧
Yeah,okay.
听着，这或许不关我的事 或许有关，我不知道
Maybe it's none of my business. Or maybe it is,I don't know.
我有点担心你
I'm worried about you.
这不是第一次 有人跟我说过这件事情了
This isn't the first time somebody said something to me about this.
我老是为我自己找一些藉口 像“跟朋友在一起才喝”
But I always made excuses,like "I'm just a social drinker."
或“来嘛，今天是国庆日”
Or "Come on,it's Flag Day!"
那你现在怎么说呢？
So,what are you saying now?
我猜我要说…
I guess I'm saying...
…我戒戒看
... I'll try and quit.
我喜欢你担心我的样子
I like that you worry about me.
发生什么事了？
So,what's going on?
我要试着戒酒了
I am gonna try and quit drinking.
哦，为什么呢？
Oh! Why?
猜猜谁又重回演艺圈了？
Guess who's back in show biz!
罗伦格林
Lorne Greene?
不是，菲比 你知道为什么吗？他死了
No. You know why? Because he's dead.
天啊
Oh,no.
我猜这似乎有点苦乐参半…
This is gonna seem bittersweet now...
是乔伊
... but Joey,that's who!
是啊，我经纪人叫我去 “我们的日子”试镜看看
My agent called with an audition for Days Of Our Lives!
-了不起 -敬乔伊
-Kick ass! -Here's to Joey!
这里，乔伊
Here Joey!
那我们必须要庆祝 应该开个肥皂剧主题派对
We have to celebrate! We should do a soap opera theme.
对，我们可以一起上床 然后其中一个人失去记忆（肥皂剧惯用情节）
We could all sleep together,then one of us could get amnesia!
瑞秋，你什么时候下班？ 晚上一起做点什么
When do you get off? We'll do something tonight.
事实上，我已经下班了 但我有其他计划
Well,actually,I'm already done. But I kind of got plans.
你有别的朋友
You have other friends?
对，我…我有约会
I have a date.
什么？
What?
-你有约会？-是的，我有约会
-You have a date?.-Yes! I have a date.
跟男人？
With a man?
不，跟一个烤面包
No, with a crouton.
-怎么？ 我有约会有什么奇怪的？-跟烤面包？
-What's so strange about me having a date?-With a crouton?
那罗斯怎么办？
What about Ross?
你还在为列单子的事 在跟他生气，是不是？
You're still mad because he made that list?
不…我不生气了
No,no,I'm not mad at him.
我对他再也不怎么了
I'm not really "anything" at him anymore.
你在胡说些什么？ 我不知道
-What are you talking about? -I don't know.
不管我从前怎么样，我…
Whatever I was feeling,I'm...
…不了
... not.
你们就差一点点了
But you guys came so close.
我知道，对不起啦，各位 你们必须得习惯…
I'm sorry. You'll have to get used to the fact...
…我不会跟罗斯约会这个事实
...that I will not be dating Ross.
他来了
Here he is.
各位，这是洛斯
Guys,this is Russ.
艾斯黛・雷纳德明星经纪
Estelle Leonard Talent Agency.
塞米，你能不能别再给我打电话了
Sammy would you stop calling me already.
不…我不是说你没才华 你非常有才华
I'm not saying you're not talented. You're very talented.
只是那只鸟死了之后 剩下的戏就很少了
But with the bird dead and all,there's very little act left.
亲爱的，放我一马，好吗？
Honey,give me a break,will you?
我等会儿再打给你
I'll talk to you later.
我最喜爱的客户来了
There's my favorite client!
告诉我，亲爱的 试镜结果如何？
So tell me,darling,how was the audition?
我觉得进行得满顺利的 他们要我周四复试
I think it went well. I got a callback for Thursday.
乔伊，你见过我心醉神迷吗？
Joey! Have you ever seen me ecstatic?
那你见识看看
Well,here it is.
对了，有件事我想跟你谈谈
Okay! Listen,there's something I want to talk to you about.
电视台的选角小姐…
The casting lady
罗莉是不是很棒？
Oh,isn't Lori a doll?
对…她很棒
She's great.
可是…我有点觉得 她好像对我有那么一点点意思
But I kind of got the feeling that she was sort of coming on to me.
我觉得如果我想得到 那个角色的话，就要…
And I definitely would get the part if I were to,you know....
派我的“小将军”出马
If I sent the little general in.
我懂了 我现在就打个电话…
I see! Well,I'm just gonna put in a call here...
…把事情搞清楚 看看究竟是怎么回事
...and we'll find out what's going on and straighten it out.
你好啊，请接罗莉
Lori,please.
亲爱的
Hi,darling!
乔伊崔比亚尼适不适合 计程车司机那个角色？
How about Joey Tribbiani for the part of the cab driver?
他是不是棒透了？
Isn't he terrific?
我们等会儿再谈
Okay,doll,talk to you later.
对，你必须跟她上床
You're gonna have to sleep with her.
你怎么了？ 是搞笑巴比
-What's the matter? -Fun Bobby.
怎么？他又喝酒了？
What? Isn't he sober?
他是没喝酒
Oh,he's sober all right.
只是我发现 搞笑巴比搞笑是有原因的
Turns out that Fun Bobby was fun for a reason.
拿去吧，亲爱的
All right,here you go,sweetie.
谢了 要不要听一个有趣的故事？
Thanks. You wanna hear something funny?
哦上帝啊，要
Oh,God,yes!
只要一过了午夜 这附近的五金行就全都关门了
There are no hardware stores open past midnight in the Village.
好好笑哦
That is funny.
前几天晚上我需要买一把锤子 我就出去在这附近逛了一逛
I needed to buy a hammer and I'm out walking around the neighborhood.
我一直走，一直走…
And I'm walking, and I'm walking...
一直走，一直走…
你是说你一直在走
So you're saying you were walking.
但…显然
But apparently...
这附近所有的五金行 一过了午夜之后都关门了
...there are no hardware stores open past midnight in the Village.
这真是个有帮助的事实
So it's a helpful fact...
而且很搞笑
...as well as funny
亲爱的，你不是该去面试了吗？
Don't you have to be at your interview?
是呀
Oh,yeah.
各位再见了
See you guys.
拜拜…
Bye...
…无聊至极的巴比
...ridiculously dull Bobby.
老天啊
Oh,my God.
他还没那么糟啦
He's not that bad.
没那么糟？ 你没有听到那个锤子的故事吗？
Not that bad? Did you not hear the hammer story?
别那么挑剔嘛
Okay,don't get all squinky.
也许你应该身历其境 才会觉得好笑啊
Maybe it's the kind of story where you had to be there.
但我下半辈子…
But I'm gonna be there!
都会身历其境啊
For the rest of my life.
我不能跟他分手，我叫他戒酒 所以他无聊是因为我
I can't dump him. I made him quit drinking. I made him dull!
好了，别这么说了
Don't say that.
也许他一直很无聊，你只是…
He's probably always been dull. You just,you know...
…把他解放了
...set it free.
罗斯
Hey,Ross.
洛斯
Hi,Russ.
再清理两张桌子 我们就可以走了，好吗？
I've got two more tables to clean,and then we'll go.
我就坐这儿好了…
I'll just sit here and...
跟你的…
...chat with your...
…好朋友一起聊天
...friend-type people.
瑞秋
Rachel?
你知道你在干什么吗？
So,you know what you're doing,right?
服务生？
Waitressing?
是，又不是…
Well,yeah. But,no. I mean....
洛斯会不会 让你想起某个人来呢？
Doesn't Russ just remind you of someone?
鲍勃萨吉特？（著名影星）
Bob Saget?
对呀
Oh,yeah!
不对…
No,no,no!
天呀
Oh,my,oh!
怎么了？
What's wrong?
她心情不好是因为…
She's upset because...
…她不小心 把一只蜘蛛涂在吐司上了
...she buttered a spider into her toast this morning.
好吧
All right.
听我说，菲比，这不要紧的
Listen,Pheebs. This is gonna be okay.
罗斯，洛斯 洛斯，罗斯
Ross,Russ. Russ,Ross.
你是…瑞秋的朋友？
Are you a friend of Rachel's?
是，我是
Yes. Yes,I am.
你是…瑞秋的朋友吗？
Are you a friend of Rachel's?
事实上，我是…
Actually,I'm kind of a...
…可以说是…
...you know...
瑞秋的约会对象…
...a date-type thing...
…朋友
...of Rachel's.
约会？
A date?
对，她的约会对象
I'm her date.
你是…你是…
Oh! Oh,you're a....
她约会的对象
Oh,you're the date.
其实这也很好…
This is actually good...
因为万一我们失去了罗斯 还有一个备用的
... because if we lose Ross,we have a spare.
你是那个…古生物学家
Oh! You are the paleontologist.
对，我是 那你是…
Yes. Yes,I am. And you are a....
牙科医师
Periodontist.
瞧，现在他们简直是黑夜跟…
See? Now they're as different as night and...
…更黑的夜
...Iater that night.
我现在要去…拿杯饮料
Well,I am going to get a beverage.
很高兴…很高兴认识你
It was nice meeting you.
彼此
Ditto.
我…我见过洛斯了
Well,I met Russ.
我不知道我们彼此在跟别人交往
Hey,I didn't know we were seeing other people.
我们又没有在交往，所以…
Well,we're not seeing each other,so....
我告诉你好了 我们博物馆里有个女的…
For your information,there's a woman at the museum...
…负责蛾类…
...who's curator of moths and other...
…跟其他有翅生物…
...winged things...
…她明显地表示她喜欢我 就像是…
...who's let it be known that she is drawn to me,much like a...
你知道嘛
...you know.
我到现在还跟她保持距离 但是如果你要这样的话…
I've kept her at bay,but if this is the deal
对，我要这样
This is the deal.
那好，祝你有愉快的一晚
Okay,well,have a nice evening.
洛斯，你好了吗？
Russ,you ready?
她在约会？
She's dating?
对，对 但你看到她在跟谁约会了吗？
Yes,but did you see who she was dating?
什么意思？
What do you mean?
你看不出来吗？ 看什么？
-Do you not see it? -See what?
我真搞不懂 她看中那花生哪一点
I don't know what she sees in that goober!
那…那个家伙…
It takes him,what? Like,I don't know...
…讲完一句话要等一个礼拜
... hello,a week to get out a sentence?
是呀，烦死人了，是不是？
It's annoying,isn't it?
我猜你没有得到那个角色…
You didn't get the part...
…或是意大利来电说它饿了
...or ltaly called and said it was hungry?
不，我要的话那角色就是我的
The part's mine if I want it.
老天啊
Oh,my God!
对呀，只要我愿意 跟选角小姐上床的话
If I'm willing to sleep with the casting lady.
我的…
Oh,my...
老天啊？
...God?
我等了十年 才等到这个机会，钱德
Ten years I've been waiting for a break like this. Ten years!
我是说“我们的日子” 那真的会在电视上播出
I mean,Days of our Lives. That's actually on television!
那你要怎么做？
What are you gonna do?
我可以跟她上床…
I guess I could sleep with her. I mean....
但我怎么能那么做呢
How can I do that?
我有一本 教我关于性的一切的立体书
I've got a pop-up book that told me everything I need to know.
我从没有为了角色 跟人家上床过
I've never slept with someone for a part.
那么她是…
Well,is she
抱歉
Sorry.
她长得好看吗？
Is she good-looking?
好看，她长得非常的好看 若我在酒吧认识她的话…
She's totally good-looking. If I met her in a bar...
…我一定会请她吃早餐
... I'd be buying her breakfast.
你知道，我是说跟她上床之后的早晨
After having slept with her.
乔伊，或许这没什么大不了的
Maybe this isn't such a big deal.
依我看你不但得到一份好工作 还可以跟她上床
The way that I see it is,you get a great job,and you get to have sex!
也许再加上一棵树跟一个胖子 你就得到圣诞节了
Throw in a tree and a fat guy,and you've got Christmas!
我只是不希望 那样得到这份工作
I just don't think that I want it that way,though.
就说有一天万一我成名好了
I mean,let's say I do make it,all right?
我会怀疑那到底是因为 我的才华，还是因为我的…
I'll always look back and wonder if it was because of my talent or...
…你知道，我的小将军
...you know,the little general.
你以前不是叫它 “小少校”的吗？
Didn't you used to call it "the little major"?
对呀，但是在上过狄丹妮后 它就升级了
After Denise DeMarco,I had to promote it.
两位要不要来一杯酒啊？
Something from the bar?
好，我要点杯酒
Yes,I would like something.
不，不，谢谢
No. No,thank you.
没关系，你想喝酒的话 我没问题，我要习惯这种事
If you wanna drink,it's okay with me. I've gotta get used to it.
不…真的 我觉得这样不好
No,no,really. I wouldn't feel right about it.
来杯水好了
Just some water,please.
-我的电冰箱的灯坏了… -来杯威士忌加冰块跟柠檬
-So my refrigerator light's out. -Scotch on the rocks with a twist!
这个游戏很有趣吧，罗斯？
We're having some fun now,huh,Ross?
我们再做一个好不好，洛斯？
Wanna do another one? Huh,Russ?
十一个字母
Eleven letters...
它的原子序号码是101 字尾是“IUM”
...atomic element number 101,ends in "ium."
是镝
Dysprosium.
镝？
试试钔吧
Try mendelevium.
二号参赛者答对了
And weenie number two has it.
除非“白缎骑士”（穆迪布鲁的歌曲） 是“杜迪布鲁”唱的
Unless "Knights in White Satin" was sung by the Doody Blues.
你真的看不出来吗？
You don't see it? You actually don't see it?
什么？
What?
你在跟罗斯约会
Honey,you're dating Ross.
不，菲比，我跟洛斯约会
No,Pheebs,I'm dating Russ.
洛斯就是罗斯，洛斯，罗斯
Russ is Ross. Russ,Ross.
史提，史里
Steve,sleeve.
没有人叫史里
No one is named sleeve.
菲比，你到底在说什么？
What are you talking about?
除了名字相似之外 对不起，我看不到你看到的
Other than their names being similar,I do not see what you're seeing.
我老实告诉你好了…
For your information...
…是赌棍 不是老千
...it's a card sharp,not a card shark.
你错得不可能再错
You could not be more wrong.
你可以试，可是你不会成功
You could try,but you would not be successful.
我先倒杯咖啡 然后再回来看你们互戳眼睛
I'm gonna get some more coffee before the pinching and eye-poking begins.
我知道问题在哪儿了
I know your problem.
是吗？
Oh,you do,do you?
你嫉妒
You're jealous.
嫉妒什么？
Of what?
你嫉妒我是个真正的医生（与罗斯的“博士”同词）
You're jealous because I'm a real doctor.
你是牙龈的医生
Hey,you're a doctor of gums.
那是人能够研究的 最小的人体器官
That's the smallest body part you can major in.
就像是第一天教你用牙线 第二天，这是你的文凭
Day one,floss. Day two,here's your diploma.
你给我听着…
You listen here
不，让我说完 不，你让我说完
-Let me finish. -No,let me finish.
不，你让我说完…
No,you let me fin
乔伊走时有没有说打算怎么做
Did Joey say what he was gonna do?
没有，我想他自己也不知道
I don't even think he knew.
你会为一个很棒的工作 跟别人上床吗？
Would you sleep with somebody to get a great job?
我必须跟谁上床？
Who would I have to sleep with?
我
Me.
我干嘛得跟你上床？
Why with you?
这是我的事 这工作你到底要不要？
It's my game. You want the job or not?
早
Good morning.
你去哪里？
Where you going?
我要跟巴比去小木屋度周末 记得吗？
Bobby and I are going away for the weekend. Remember?
带那么多酒干什么？
What's with all the liquor?
打扰一下，小姐
Excuse me, miss
如果被这些液体淹了，这个座位可以用做漂浮设备吗？
In a water landing, can this seat be used as a flotation device?
怎么了？巴比又开始喝酒了
What's going on? Is Bobby drinking again?
不…这不是他喝的 这是给我的
This is not for him. This is for me.
这样他会很清醒，而我会觉得 他的鞋带笑话好笑多了
That way,he's sober but his shoelace stories are more amusing.
天哪，他连敲门 怎么都这么乏味啊
God! Even his knock is boring!
我马上就好了 我可以跟你谈一谈吗？
-I'll be ready in a second. -Could I talk to you?
可以啊
Sure.
这真的很难开口
This is hard for me to say.
天啊，你又开始喝酒了
You fell off the wagon!
不是…
Oh,no,no.
是关于你的
It's about you.
我怎么了？
What about me?
我想你或许有酗酒问题
I think you may have a drinking problem.
不，这些是…
What,these?
…擦伤口用的
No,these are for cuts and scrapes.
我现在无法扯入一段 相互依赖的关系当中
Look,I'm not strong enough to be in a codependent relationship.
该死
Oh,shoot.
不管怎么样 我希望我们还是朋友
Well,anyway,I hope we can be friends.
保重了
Take care.
你也是 拜
-You too. -Goodbye.
怎么了？
What happened?
我们分手了
We kind of broke up.
这些酒谁要？
Does anybody want these?
我拿一瓶
I'll take one.
我有时候喜欢拿这种东西 假装我是个巨人
Sometimes I hold stuff like this and pretend I'm a giant.
复试结果怎么样？
How'd the callback go?
简直不可思议，我一进去 她就开始对我上下其手
It was unbelievable. I walked in there and she was all over me.
结果呢？ 我就是办不到
-What did you do? -I couldn't do it.
我告诉她我不想那样得到角色
I didn't want the part that way.
干得好…
Good for you!
等等，我离开她办公室之后
But wait! I left her office...
她追出我来说要给我一个更重要的角色
...and she caught up with me and offered me a bigger part.
所以呢？
So,and?
所以… 各位面前站的是德瑞克雷莫瑞医生，神经外科医师
So,you are now looking at Dr. Drake Ramoray,neurosurgeon...
…至少会在四集里面出镜
... recurring in at least four episodes!
太棒了…我去洗澡了
All right,I gotta go shower.
你们听说我被瑞秋甩了吧？
I guess you guys heard Rachel dumped me.
是呀，很遗撼啊，老兄
Yeah,I'm sorry,man.
她说我会让她想起另外一个人
She said I remind her too much of somebody.
你们知道那个人是谁吗？
Any idea who she's talking about?
我知道，是…鲍勃萨吉特
Oh,I do. It's Bob Saget.
她恨他
She hates him.
茱莉
Hey,Julie!
最近好吗？
How are you doing?
我不知道 没有了罗斯，的确很不对劲…
I don't know. It's weird not being with Ross...
…但是我猜我还好啦
... but I guess I'm doing okay.
事实上 我带了一些他的东西…
Actually,I've got some of his stuff that he....
-我们认识吗？ -好像不
-Have we met?.-I don't think so.
你看起来好面熟
You look so familiar.
也许我们可以来杯咖啡谈谈这一点
Well, maybe we could talk about it over a cup of coffee.
知道吗，我讨厌咖啡
Know what?. I'm sick of coffee.
我们去喝点果汁吧
Let's go get us some juice.
-好  -好
-All right.-Okay.
-再见 -再见
-Bye -Bye.